A Guide to the John H. Knowles Papers FA047
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Massachusetts General Hospital, 1947-1972 1959-1971; 2; 22.6 Cubic Feet
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Professional, B
    - Associated Harvard Alumni - Committee on Patterns of Hospital Services, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 224)
    - Association for Improving the Medical Resources of Outer Cape Cod, 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 225)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges - Institute Talk, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 226)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges - Institute Talk, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 227)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges - Nominating Committee, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 228)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges - Second Institute on Medical Center Administrative Problems, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 229)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges - Testimony on Federal Support of Health Research, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 230)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges - Workshop on Education of the Physician, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 231)
    - Atlanta - New Orleans Talk, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 232)
    - "Atlantic Monthly", 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 233)
    - "Balanced Biology of the Teaching Hospital" - Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 234)
    - Barnes, Allen C., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 235)
    - Barnes Hospital, 1962-1966 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Barnes Hospital, 1962-1966 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Belmont Hill School, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 238)
    - Berkshire County Tuberculosis Association (Box 20, Folder 239)
    - Beryllium Poisoning Study, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - Beryllium Poisoning Study, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - Bird, Dr. Kenneth T., 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Blue Ribbon Study Commission to Review Hospital Costs, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 243)
    - Book Orders, 1965-1971 (Box 20, Folder 244)
    - Boston Broadcasters, Inc., 1961-1966, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 245)
    - Boston City Hospital, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 246)
    - Boston City Hospital - Supplemental Material (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - Boston City Hospital - Ten Year Building Program, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - Boston City Hospital Diary, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Boston Committee on Foreign Relations, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - Boston Garden Arena Corporation - Board of Directors, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - "Boston Globe", 1962-1965, 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Boston Herald, 1962, 1964-1969 (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - Boston Library Society, 1964, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Boston - New York City Talks, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Boston Patriots, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - "Boston Record - American", 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Boston Tuberculosis Association, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - Boston Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1961-1964, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Boys Club of Boston - Board of Overseers, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 260)
    - Bronchoscopy - Endoscopy, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 261)
    - Buffalo - New York City Talks, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 262)
    - Bunker, Dr. John, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 263)
    - Burbank Hospital, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 264)
    - "California Medicine", 1969 (Box 22, Folder 265)
    - Canterbury Society, 1961, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 266)
    - Chase Frontier Fund, Inc., 1968 (Box 22, Folder 267)
    - Chicago Trip, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 268)
      Northwestern, Bensinger Search Committee, Harvard.
    - Cleveland State University - Health Sciences Feasibility Study, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 269)
    - Clinicopathological Conferences, 1961-1966, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - Committee on the Study of Academic Radiology - National Academy of Sciences, 1963, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 272)
    - Committee on the Study of Academic Radiology - National Academy of Sciences, 1963, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 273)
    - Congressional Subcommittee on Fiscal Policy - "Medical Costs", 1969 (Box 22, Folder 274)
    - Consultations, 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 275)
    - Cornell - Alpha Omega Alpha Lecture, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 276)
    - Council of Foundations, Inc., 1971 (Box 23, Folder 277)
    - Council on the Department of Public Health, 1963-1966 (Box 23, Folder 278)
    - "Daedalus", 1963, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 279)
    - Diffusion, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 280)
    - Duke University Medical Center - Board of Visitors, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 281)
    - Duke University Medical Center - Board of Visitors, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 282)
    - Duke University Medical Center - Board of Visitors, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 283)
    - Duke University Medical Center - Board of Visitors, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 284)
    - Educational Enrichment Program, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 285)
    - Endicott House Report of Summer Study on Education, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 286)
    - Evanston Hospital - Ruth Gray Lecture, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 287)
    - Fan Letters, 1965-1968 (Box 24, Folder 288)
    - Field and Cowles Insurance, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 289)
    - Finnegan, George T., 1961 (Box 24, Folder 290)
    - Gas Club, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 291)
    - General Correspondence, March 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 292)
    - General Correspondence, March 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 293)
    - General Correspondence, March 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 294)
    - General Correspondence, May 1968-February 1970 (Box 25, Folder 295)
    - General Correspondence, May 1968-February 1970 (Box 25, Folder 296)
    - General Correspondence, May 1968-February 1970 (Box 25, Folder 297)
    - General Correspondence, May 1968-February 1970 (Box 25, Folder 298)
    - General Correspondence, May 1968-February 1970 (Box 25, Folder 299)
    - General Correspondence, 1961-April 1968 (Box 26, Folder 300)
    - General Correspondence, 1961-April 1968 (Box 26, Folder 301)
    - General Correspondence, 1961-April 1968 (Box 26, Folder 302)
    - General Correspondence, 1961-April 1968 (Box 26, Folder 303)
    - General Rose Memorial Hospital, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 304)
    - Gerbig, Robert, 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 305)
    - Gerbig, Robert, 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 306)
    - Glaser, Dr. Robert J., 1960-1967 (Box 26, Folder 307)
    - "Good Housekeeping", 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 308)
    - GOP Party Platform - Health Committee, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 309)
    - Governor's Steering Committee on Social Problems (New York), 1970 (Box 27, Folder 310)
    - Greater Boston Chamber of Commerce - National Advisory Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 311)
    - Greater Boston Hospital Council, Inc., 1963-1966, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 312)
    - Grolier Society, Inc., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 313)
    - Group Health Association of America, Inc., 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 314)
    - Hahnemann Medical College of Philadelphia - Commencement, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 315)
    - "Handbook of Medical Sociology", 1970 (Box 27, Folder 316)
    - Harbor National Bank of Boston, 1963-1968 (Box 27, Folder 317)
    - Harbor National Bank of Boston, 1963-1968 (Box 27, Folder 318)
    - Hardy, Dr. Harriet L. (Box 27, Folder 319)
    - Harris, Seymour E. (Box 27, Folder 320)
    - Harrison's Textbook - Diseases of the Chest, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 321)
    - Harrison's Textbook - First Draft (Box 28, Folder 322)
    - Harrison's Textbook - Final Draft and Criticisms, October-December 1960 (Box 28, Folder 323)
    - Harrison's Textbook - Final Draft and Criticisms, October-December 1960 (Box 28, Folder 324)
    - Harrison's Textbook - Rewrites, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 325)
    - Harrison's Textbook - Rewrites, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 326)
    - Harrison's Textbook - Revisions, 1960-1968 (Box 28, Folder 327)
    - Harvard Alumni Association, 1961-1965 (Box 29, Folder 328)
    - Harvard Alumni Association, 1961-1965 (Box 29, Folder 329)
    - Harvard Alumni Association - Committee to Nominate Overseers and Directors, 1964-1965 (Box 29, Folder 330)
    - Harvard Alumni Association - Committee to Nominate Overseers and Directors, 1964-1965 (Box 29, Folder 331)
    - Harvard Club, 1959-1966 (Box 29, Folder 332)
    - Harvard Fund Council, 1961-1967 (Box 29, Folder 333)
    - Harvard Institute of Politics, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 334)
    - Harvard Medical College - Los Angeles, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 335)
    - Harvard Medical School - Admissions, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 336)
    - Harvard Medical School - Faculty, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 337)
    - Harvard Medical School - Faculty Meetings, 1963-1967 (Box 29, Folder 338)
    - Harvard Medical School - 2nd Year Lectures - Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 339)
    - Harvard Medical School - 2nd Year Lectures, 1960-1963 (Box 30, Folder 340)
    - Harvard Medical School - 2nd Year Lectures, 1960-1963 (Box 30, Folder 341)
    - Harvard Medical School - 2nd Year Lectures, 1960-1963 (Box 30, Folder 342)
    - Harvard Medical School - 3rd Year Lectures, 1960-1962 (Box 30, Folder 343)
    - Harvard Medical School - 4th Year Lectures, 1959-1963 (Box 30, Folder 344)
    - Harvard Medical Society, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 345)
    - Harvard University - Absence Policy, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 346)
    - Harvard University - Philips Brooks House Association, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 347)
    - Harvard University - Thorndike Memorial Laboratory, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 348)
    - Harvard University Press, 1957-1965, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 349)
    - Hatch, Francis W., Jr., 1967 (Box 30, Folder 350)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, undated (Box 30, Folder 351)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, July 20-September 9, 1969, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 352)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, June 20-July 19, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 353)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, June 20-July 19, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 354)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, June 20-July 19, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 355)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, June 20-July 19, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 356)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, June 20-July 19, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 357)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, June 20-July 19, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 358)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, November 1968-June 19, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 359)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, November 1968-June 19, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 360)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Clippings, November 1968-June 19, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 361)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Correspondence, July 1-August 11, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 362)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Correspondence, July 1-August 11, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 363)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Correspondence, July 1-August 11, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 364)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Correspondence, July 1-August 11, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 365)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Correspondence, January-June 30, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 366)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Correspondence, January-June 30, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 367)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Correspondence, January-June 30, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 368)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Correspondence, January-June 30, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 369)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Correspondence, January-June 30, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 370)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Correspondence, January-June 30, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 371)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Kook Letters, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 372)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - Speech Notes (Box 34, Folder 373)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Correspondence, January 1969-October 1971 (Box 34, Folder 374)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 1 (Box 34, Folder 375)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 2 (Box 34, Folder 376)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 2 (Box 34, Folder 377)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 4 (Box 34, Folder 378)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 5 (Box 34, Folder 379)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 5 (Box 34, Folder 380)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 6 (Box 34, Folder 381)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 7 (Box 35, Folder 382)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 7 (Box 35, Folder 383)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 7 (Box 35, Folder 384)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Chapter 7 (Box 35, Folder 385)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Medicaid Chapter (Box 35, Folder 386)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Medicaid Chapter (Box 35, Folder 387)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Medicaid Chapter (Box 35, Folder 388)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Medicaid Chapter (Box 36, Folder 389)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Population Chapter (Box 36, Folder 390)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Population Chapter (Box 36, Folder 391)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Summary and Epilog (Box 36, Folder 392)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Summary and Epilog (Box 36, Folder 393)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Additional Information (Box 36, Folder 394)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Notes (Box 36, Folder 395)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dr. Knowles' Journal" - Typescript (Incomplete) (Box 36, Folder 396)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Life" Article, July 1, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 397)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "Dealing with the Department of Health, Education and Welfare" (Box 37, Folder 398)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "The Knowles Controversy" by Ann Marie Curran, Gerarda M. Fulham, Nancy L. Schubert (Box 37, Folder 399)
    - Health Education and Welfare (HEW) Appointment Controversy - "The Rejection of Dr. Knowles: A Study in Political Influence" by Charles B. Goodwin, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 400)
    - Health, Inc. (Box 37, Folder 401)
    - Health Industries Association, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 402)
    - Health Services for the Poor, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 403)
    - Health Services for the Poor - Advisory Panel, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 404)
    - Hemophilia Association, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 405)
    - Henry Ford Hospital, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 406)
    - Hospital Association of Rhode Island, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 407)
    - Hospital Inspection and Certification Program, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 408)
    - Hospital Insurance Coverage, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 409)
    - Hospital Planning for Greater Boston, 1966-1968 (Box 37, Folder 410)
    - "Hospital Practice" - Editorial Board, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 411)
    - Hospital Superintendent's Club, 1963, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 412)
    - House-Senate Finance Committee Testimony - Medical Costs, 1967-1969 (Box 38, Folder 413)
    - House Ways and Means Committee Statement, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 414)
    - Idiopathic Pulmonary Hemosiderosis, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 415)
    - "Image" Article, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 416)
    - Institute for American Democracy, Inc. - Board of Sponsors, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 417)
    - Institute of Medicine, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 418)
    - Ithaca College - Commencement, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 419)
    - James Jackson Putnam Children's Center, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 420)
    - Johns Hopkins Medical Institutions, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 421)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Deanship Offer, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 422)
    - Joint Economic Committee - Medical Costs Testimony, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 423)
    - "Journal of Chronic Diseases", 1965-1967 (Box 38, Folder 424)
    - "Journal of the American Medical Association", 1959, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 425)
    - Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1962-1966 (Box 38, Folder 426)
    - Kappa Phi Eta, 1962-1966, 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 427)
    - Kennedy Action Corps, 1969-1971 (Box 38, Folder 428)
    - Kennedy Foundation Symposium, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 429)
    - Kennedy Laboratories, 1962-1964 (Box 38, Folder 430)
    - Kennedy Scholarship Steering Committee, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 431)
    - Klainer, Dr. Laurence M., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 432)
    - Lecture Requests, May 1966-1971 (Box 38, Folder 433)
    - Lecture Requests, May 1966-1971 (Box 38, Folder 434)
    - Lecture Requests, 1961-April 1966 (Box 39, Folder 435)
    - Lecture Requests, 1961-April 1966 (Box 39, Folder 436)
    - Little, Brown and Company, 1961-1963 (Box 39, Folder 437)
    - "Look" Interview, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 438)
    - Lovatt Memorial Laboratories - Visit, 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 439)
    - Lowell Lectures, 1958, 1961-1963 (Box 39, Folder 440)
    - Lowell Lectures - Dinner, Reservations, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 441)
    - Lowell Lectures - Publicity, 1963-1965, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 442)
    - Lowell Lectures - Speakers, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 443)
    - Lowell Lectures - Speakers, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 444)
    - Massachusetts Blue Cross, 1962-1967 (Box 40, Folder 445)
    - Massachusetts Federation of Nursing Homes, Inc. - Advisory Council, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 446)
    - Massachusetts Hospital Association - Board of Trustees - Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 447)
    - Massachusetts Hospital Association - Joint Meeting with Massachusetts Medical Society, 1963-1966 (Box 40, Folder 448)
    - Massachusetts Hospital Association - Joint Meeting with Massachusetts Medical Society, 1963-1966 (Box 40, Folder 449)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Humanities Seminar, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 450)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Visiting Committee, 1963-1967 (Box 40, Folder 451)
    - Massachusetts Medical Society, 1962-1966 (Box 40, Folder 452)
    - Massachusetts Medical Society - Medicare and the DeBakey Report, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 453)
    - Massachusetts Memorial Hospitals, 1963, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 454)
    - Massachusetts Souther's Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 40, Folder 455)
    - Massachusetts Thoracic Society, 1959-1962 (Box 41, Folder 456)
    - McLean Hospital Rehabilitation Center Dedication, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 457)
    - McLean Hospital Report, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 458)
    - Means, Dr. J. Howard, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 459)
    - MEDEX (Medicin Extension = Physician Extension) Program, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 460)
    - Medical Administrator's Conference, 1965-1968 (Box 41, Folder 461)
    - Medical Clinics of North America, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 462)
    - Medical Education for National Defense, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 463)
    - Medical Exchange Club, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 464)
    - "Medical World News" - Editorial Advisory Board, 1969-1971 (Box 41, Folder 465)
    - Medical Foundation, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 41, Folder 466)
    - Medicare Bill - H.R. 1, January 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 467)
    - Medicare Bill - H.R. 1, January 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 468)
    - Medicare Bill - H.R. 1, January 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 469)
    - Medicare - Senate Subcommittee Testimony (July 18, 1969), 1968-1970 (Box 42, Folder 470)
    - Medicare - Senate Subcommittee Testimony (July 18, 1969), 1968-1970 (Box 42, Folder 471)
    - Middlesex County Sanitarium, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 472)
    - Misericordia - Fordham Hospitals Talk, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 473)
    - Modern University Symposium - Geneva, 1967-1968 (Box 42, Folder 474)
    - Montreal General Hospital - 150th Anniversary, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 475)
    - Mt. Sinai - Commencement, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 476)
    - National Advisory Council for Hampshire College, 1969-1971 (Box 42, Folder 477)
    - National Board Examinations, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 478)
    - National Council of Senior Citizens - National Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 479)
    - National Cyclopedia of American Biography, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 480)
    - National Jewish Hospital, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 481)
    - Navy League of the United States - Boston Council, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 482)
    - Newcomen Society, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 483)
    - "New England Journal of Medicine", 1959-1970 (Box 42, Folder 484)
    - New York Academy of Medicine - Committee on Special Studies, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 485)
    - New York City Hospitals - Barney Report, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 486)
    - New York Medical College, 1966, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 487)
    - New York University - Vice Presidency Offer, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 488)
    - New York University - Medical Center, 1965-1967 (Box 43, Folder 489)
    - Nolan, James J. - Account, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 490)
    - Nuffield Provincial Hospital Trust Symposium, Birmingham, England, 1963-1967 (Box 43, Folder 491)
    - Nu Sigma Nu - Baltimore, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 492)
    - Oldster Data, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 493)
    - Pan-American Medical Association, Inc., 1964 (Box 43, Folder 494)
    - Patients, 1959-1964 (Box 43, Folder 495)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Permanently restricted - Confidential material.
    - Pediatric Postgraduate Course - Advances in Pulmonary Physiology, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 496)
    - Pharos of Alpha Omega Alpha, 1963-1971 (Box 43, Folder 497)
    - Pleural Biopsey (Box 43, Folder 498)
    - Pope, Dr. Alfred - Selected Publications, 1959-1963 (Box 43, Folder 499)
    - Possible Projects (Box 43, Folder 500)
    - Postgraduate Course in Pulmonary Function - Boston City Hospital, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 501)
    - Postgraduate Course in Pulmonary Function - Boston City Hospital, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 502)
    - Postgraduate Courses - Massachusetts General Hospital, 1958-1965 (Box 44, Folder 503)
    - Postgraduate Courses - Massachusetts General Hospital, 1958-1965 (Box 44, Folder 504)
    - Postgraduate Courses - Massachusetts General Hospital, 1958-1965 (Box 44, Folder 505)
    - Postgraduate Courses - Massachusetts General Hospital, 1958-1965 (Box 44, Folder 506)
    - President's Committee on Health Education - Testimony (January 6, 1972) (Box 44, Folder 507)
    - Project Hope, 1962-1963 (Box 44, Folder 508)
    - Pulmonary Clinic, 1959-1962 (Box 44, Folder 509)